Good afternoon Hello I'm from Ukraine, the city of
Добрый день Привет Я из Украины город
Khmelnitsky, the city of Vodka, Russia, I'm from the
Хмельницкий водского города России я
city of St. Petersburg And from St. Petersburg before I saw it
города Петербург А с Питера до свидел ли
from Russia, I'll ask how you feel about the
из России спрошу как вы относитесь к
war in Ukraine
войне в Украине
as a war in Russia of the entire
как к войне в России всего
civilized world
цивилизованного мира
Well, that is, you support it or
Ну то есть вы поддержите ее или
condemn it and consider
осуждаете и считайте
it right  Dasha, your country led
что правильно Даша ваша страна вела
troops to Ukraine
войска в Украину
because of which you support Here is your position
из-за чего поддержите Вот ваша позиция
now at such a time we are dividing the
сейчас такое время у нас идет деление
world the
мира
world is becoming bipolar at one time the
мир становится двухполярным свое время
Soviet Union lost the Cold War
Советский Союз проиграл холодную войну
to the states So the states became the world
до штатам Вот и штаты стали мировым
hegemon Russia did not agree with this
гегемоном Россия с этим не согласилась
So after 2000  I
Вот и после 2000-х годов
decided that it’s enough to be a victory in the
решила что хватит быть победа на
backyards of this world, it’s time to go out
задворках этого мира пора выходить тоже
into the lead too. As the
в лидирующие Как говорится
US forwards say, the
форварды США
confrontation that has now outgrown the
противостояние которое переросло сейчас
war that comes to
войну которая приходит на территории
Ukraine, that is, with the hands of the Ukrainians, the United States
Украины то есть руками украинцев США
solves problems with Russia, as I understand it,
решает проблемы с Россией Я так понимаю
that the hands of the Russians are not Ukraine Russia
что руками россиян не Украина Россия
Well  you are fighting there before us people, it
Ну вы же там бьетесь до нас люди
turns out that Biden forced Putin
получается что байден заставил Путина
to attack B  The ratsky Ukrainian people
напасть на Братский украинский народ вот
are not to blame here,
здесь не байдам виноват
yes, well, someone else made
да ну кто-то же кто-то Же заставил
Putin attack the Brotherly people Ukraine
Путина напасть на Братский народ Украина
for you Brotherly people No,
для вас Братский народ Нет
I understand, yes, that is, you just
понял да То есть вы на просто не
attacked the non-Brotherly Slavic people Yes, it’s
Братский славянский народ напали Да это
even one people I think that
даже один народ Я считаю что украинцы
Ukrainians, yes, that is, it turns out that you
вот да то есть вы получается вы на своих
, from your point of view, attacked your own Russians in
же русских вот с вашей точки зрения
such a way to kill
напали так поубивать
No, not to be punished for lawlessness
Нет не побывать наказать за беспредел
that kills, yes, that is, it turns out you
который убивает да то есть получается вы
kill, look it turns out I correctly
убиваете смотрите получается Я правильно
understood that Biden make such a
понял что байден сделать такую
multi-move that with the hands of Russians
многоходовочку что руками русских
kills other Russians  in Ukraine Yes,
убивает других русских в Украине Да
who forced Putin to send troops I
кто кто заставил Путина ввести войска Я
’m telling you the Americans specifically which one
же говорю американцы конкретно какой Кто
of the Anglo-Saxons is responsible for
из англосаксов ответственность
some unknown Anglo-Saxon
какой-то неизвестный англосак
Well, who is King Philip the Queen
Ну кто там король Филипп Королева
who died
который умерла кто
who is now Indian Prime who I
то что сейчас индус Премьер кто Я вам
explain to you all the queen’s premieres there The
объясняю все премьеры королевы там
President is talking heads  and who is not a
Президент это говорящие головы а кто не
talking head so that I understand Well,
говорящий голова чтобы я понял Ну это
these are the people we will not recognize, maybe they are not
этих людей мы не узнаем может их и нет
about  where do you know
откуда вы знаете
how do you know that they are the
откуда вы знаете что они есть
world ruled by money capital this
миром правят деньги капитал этим
capital influences I will say this is the board of
капиталом влияет я скажу так совет
directors
директоров
it is in any way people who have
он есть по-любому люди которые имеют
big money they decide the fate of who these
деньги большие они решают судьбы кто эти
people Tell us we won’t find out maybe they
люди Вот скажите мы не узнаем может их
don’t Maybe it’s aliens maybe
нет Может это инопланетяне может быть
it’s aliens sitting in control
это инопланетяне сидят управляют
Or maybe, for example,
А может например
he’s shorter, the most important thing,
он короче самое главное
here he’s a reptilian, it
вот он рептилогом
turns out that in order for me to summarize,
получается что чтобы я так под резюмирую
someone controls it all in the world, but we
кто-то управляет этим всем в мире но мы
don’t know who they don’t even imagine Who
не знаем кто им даже не представляем Кто
Yes, they didn’t even imagine everything else is
Да даже не представлял все остальное
good Or maybe then  These same
хорошо А может тогда и Путиным эти же
people rule Putin no Putin went against
люди управляют нет Путин пошел против
this system and this is what
этой системы и вылилось это то что
Russia began to become And why did you
Россия стала становиться А почему вы
decide that Putin went against Maybe it
решили что Путин пошел против Может это
's just the concept of the golden billion to
как раз концепция золотого миллиарда
kill the Slavs like Putin was forced
поубивать славян типа и Путина заставили
to do it no the concept of the golden
это сделать нет концепция золотого
billion worked in the nineties  in
миллиарда работала в девяностые года в
Russia, when people died Yes, they
России когда люди дохли Да
propagandized from drug addiction was the
пропагандировали из наркомания была
propaganda of thousands of
пропагандами тысяч
medicine in Soviet  th Union they didn’t drink
медицина в Советском Союзе не бухали
there everything was done according to GOST everything was
там все делалось по ГОСТу все это
controlled to control the production of alcoholic
контролировать производство алкогольных
beverages everything else was
напиток всего остального было
controlled I understood naturally it was
контролировано понял естественно было
good to
хорошо
destroy the Anglo-Saxons but of
уничтожали англосакции да
course who boasted about it then that they
естественно кто этим хвастался потом что
destroyed the Soviet Union I don’t mean
развалили Советский Союз не имею в виду
Who destroyed the
Кто упаленной водкой типа уничтожал
Russian Anglo-Saxons with fallen vodka, then no
русских англосаксы то нет
who came  publicity, people began to
которые пришла гласность люди стали
use
пользоваться
some bad
какими-то вот плохими
things to make money, apply in the
вещами чтобы зарабатывать обращаться на
usual way, but it turns out that everything is so
обычном роде а получается все
damn short, the reptilian was gone, he couldn’t
блин такие короче рептилоид пропал не
stand it
выдержал
yet, you understand everyone is righteous, this is the world
еще вы поняли всем праведка это мировая
behind the scenes, but you don’t know who they exactly
за кулиса но вы не знаете кто они точно
are, but I have them like there in  closet
есть но они у меня типа там в шкафу
lives shorter than some kind of
живет короче какой-то
creatures I don’t know But it’s for sure that lives there and
существ Я не знаю Но точно там живет и
she controls me
она управляет мной
freaks
чудики
yes This is a problem here in Russia They
да Это есть проблема вот в России Они не
can’t admit their defeats to themselves they
могут себе признать свои поражения они
can’t admit that they are technologically
не могут признать что они технологически
backward so the West does not allow
отсталые вот им Запад не дает
them to develop The West does not  gives if Russia
развиваться им Запад не дает если Россия
wants to become dimonto who's stopping you,
хочет стать димонто кто вам мешает
do your t  am electronics yes There
делайте свои там электронику да Там
they all use everything western without the
они все пользуются всем западным без
whole West they were in the
всего Запада они были
seventies or 60s of the last
семидесятых или 60-х годах прошлого
century with disk phones they
Столетия с дисками телефонами они
use everything western it turns out the
пользуются всем западным получается
West specially gives the Russians
Запад специально россиянам даёт
technologies so that the Russians develop
технологии чтобы россияне э развивались
like this
так
and Russia in short means
а Россия короче значит
put against this nonsense they have  this is
поставлю против этого бред у них это
schizophrenia in my head write your version
шизофрения в голове напишите свою версию
what do you think about these
что вообще думаете про Вот таких
characters of
персонажей
the subscriber
подписчицы Ставьте лайк и залайком 3